[music]
I didn't [music] know
Uh-huh.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Come on.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. [music]
Well, good evening. [laughter] It's all good. We'll try again. Welcome. We're
trying something new. Did y'all like it? Was it fun? >> Yes. Well,
welcome to Movement Church. [music] Miracle and healing night. Are you excited?
All right. Come on. Let's [music] forget about our day. Let's worship the
Lord tonight. Okay. Here we go. Come on. Put your [music] hands
like this. I'm shaking off the heaviness.
I'm dancing out of [music and singing] my regrets. I'm throwing caution to the
wind. No, I am not [music and singing] ashamed to praise. Some say it's
foolishness,
but I say it's worth the risk. I can't forget what Jesus
[music and singing] did. No, I am not ashamed to praise. [music] I Where
[singing] are those chains I want? [music] I'm free. I'm free. I'm
free. I'm free. [music and singing] My sin is gone. How can it be?
I'm free. I'm [music] free. I'm free. [singing] free. Look at what
the Lord has done. [music] I'm never going back [singing] to the
way I was. I sing of dance [music] cuz I really I'm
free. [singing] I'm free. Thank God [music] I'm free.
[singing]
[music] I've got a friend that never quits or no one [music and singing]
love as good as this. And I don't care what anyone says.
[singing and music] I'll never be ashamed to praise like [music and singing] this. There are
those days where I'm free. I'm free. [music and singing] I'm free. I'm free.
My s
I'm free. [singing and music] I'm free. on the living with the Lord. [singing]
I am never going back to the way I was. I sing
I sing [music and singing] of I
God. I'm [music and singing] free. Lord, you took the cross and you broke
your body. [music] You shed your blood. Now [singing] the sinner can't
see. My dead is [music] laid and my record is clean. I
couldn't do it, so you did it for me. You took the
[music] cross [singing] and you broke your body. You shed your blood,
now the sin against [music] my debt is paid and my [singing]
record is I couldn't do it, [music] so you didn't cross. You
took the cross and you
shing
[music] [singing]
[music]
[singing]
[music] out. Where are [singing] those chains that won't tell me? I'm
free. I'm [music] free. I'm free. I'm free. My sin [singing] is
gone now. I'm free. [music] I'm free. I'm free. I'm free.
What the Lord has. [singing] I am never going back to the
way [music] I will sing. Sing [singing] it. I [music] free. I'm
free. >> [singing] >> God, I'm free. But you took the cross and you
[music] broke your body. You shed your blood, now the [singing] sinner
can't. My dead [music] is paid and my record is I couldn't
[singing] do it, so you did it to us. You took the
cross and you [music] Heat. Heat. Heat. [singing]
[music] [singing]
I do. So [music and singing] you did it for the only
[music]
[music] Heat. Heat. Heat.
[music] I'm never going back to the way.
Look at what [music and singing] the Lord has done. I'm never going back
to the way I [music] look at what the Lord has done.
I'm never [music] going back to the way I [singing] was. I
praise that you're free because he set you free. Amen. >> AMEN. >> AMEN.
[cheering] >> ALL RIGHT. ARE you ready to really praise tonight? Here we
go. Say >> allelujah.
>> Ready? >> Yeah. >> Here we go.
>> Hallelujah.
You get all the praise. We say hallelujah.
You get all the praise. is hallelujah. [music and singing]
You get all the praise. We say [music and singing] hallelujah.
[music] You're >> doing good. Come on. Get a [singing] little bounce in
your step. [music] Halle hallelujah. You get [singing] all the praise.
We say hallelujah.
[music] You get all the praise always. [singing] And I've got a
God who is for. [music] Oh, he's known for making way. He
fought the [music and singing] battle so I wouldn't have to. All glory belongs
to his name. I've got a God who's been faith. Oh, [music]
far more than I could have slayed. Through every season, in spite
of all my weakness, he gave me a song I can sing.
I came to praise. [music] I declare that tonight. >> I came to
praise. >> That's why I woke up today. >> That's [music] why I woke
up today. [singing] >> I came to praise. So [music]
we say hallelujah.
[music] You get all the praises we say. Amen. Amen.
[music and singing] Hallelujah. You get all the praise away. [music] And I got
a king who is risen. Oh, he put my [music] shame in
the grave. To hell and back. And now I [singing] never have
to. And he did it all in three days. I came [music]
to praise.
I came to praise. >> That's why I woke up today. >> That's why
I [music] woke up today.
>> I came to praise. So we say [music] halle
[singing] Hallelujah. You get all the praise. We say hallelujah. [music]
[singing]
You get all the praise. >> [music] >> I see the one [singing] I'm
seeing. I see [music] the battle. That's how I fight. I see
it's holy. [music] I see it twice. I see it's holy. [singing]
The rest of my
[music] night. I see the battle. That's how I fight. I [music]
see holy twice. Holy [music] the rest of my life
the rest of [music and singing] my life.
Hallelujah. [music] You get all the praise. We got everybody.
Halle Hallelujah. [music] Get all the praise. You always [singing]
[music] Hallelujah. We get all the praises we say halle
[music] [singing] hallelujah. We get all the praises away. I'm singing
morning [music and singing] sing
[music]
the rest of my life. [music] Hallel [singing] Hallelujah to give all
[music] the praise.
Come on, sing it out. [music] >> I came to praise.
>> I came to praise. [music] Get out of my way. >> Out of
my way.
>> I came to praise. >> Hallelujah. Come on, let's praise the [cheering] LORD
TONIGHT. OH, WE THANK YOU, FATHER. COME ON, lift your hands and
worship him tonight. It doesn't matter what you're going through. It doesn't
matter what battle you're facing. We worship the Lord because we know
we have the victory.
>> For mine, nailed to the cross, you crucified
all my [music and singing] sin and shame. It was washed by your mercy.
You [music] are the treasure [singing] I find,
reason for living. [music and singing] So let my life become an offering
to the one who is worthy.
Come on, let's sing it out. All praise [music] [singing] to the
Lord most high. All praise to the one [singing and music] who saved my
life. All praise to Jesus Christ, high king [music and singing] of heaven,
my king forever.
>> Stor [singing] the gates of my heart.
The veil [music] in between was torn apart. Now you hold [music]
the keys to the grave. Come on church, let's sing this. [singing]
Great things to life. And you roll stones away. [music] >> All [singing]
praise to the Lord most high. All praise to the one [music and singing]
who saved my life. All praise to Jesus Christ, high
king [music] of heaven, my king [singing] forever. All praise to the
Lord [singing and music] most high. All praise to the one who saved my
life. All praise [music and singing] to Jesus Christ, my king of heaven, [music and singing]
my king forever.
You're my king forever. We worship you, Jesus.
Lift my hands [music] and worship you. We worship [singing] you.
I lift [music and singing] my hands up. Lay my whole life down. My
[singing] whole life down is for you. I [music and singing] lift my hands
up, lay my whole life down. My whole [singing] life down [music]
is for you. And I lift my hands [music and singing] up, lay my
whole life down. My whole life down [music] is for [singing] you.
I lift my hands up, lay my whole life down. [music] Cuz
my [singing] whole life down is for you. And I lift [music and singing]
my hands up, lay my whole life down. My whole [music and singing] life
down is for you. I [singing] lift my hands up, lay my
whole life down. My whole [music and singing] life now is for you.
All praise to the [music] Lord most high. All praise [music] to
the one who [singing] saved my life. All praise to Jesus [music]
[singing] Christ, my king of heaven, my king [music and singing] forever.
All praise to the Lord most [singing] high. All praise to the
one [music] who saved my life. [singing] All praise to Jesus Christ,
my king [music] of heaven, [singing] my king forever. I lift [music]
my hands up. My [singing] whole life I [music] down is for
[singing] you. I lift my hands up. My [music] whole life down.
My whole [singing] life now is for you. [music] All praise [singing]
to the Lord most high and all praise [singing and music] to the one
who saved my life. All praise to Jesus Christ, my
king [singing] of heaven, [music] my king forever. All praise [music] to
the Lord most [singing] high. All praise to the one who saves
my life. [music] All praise to Jesus [singing] Christ, high king of
heaven, my king forever.
>> Come on, let's [music] lift our hands [singing] and worship the Lord.
You are [singing] my king. [music]
You are my king, [music and singing] Lord.
Oh, [singing] we bless [music] your name. Oh, we give you praise.
You are the same each and every [music and singing] day. So, we bless
your name, Lord. We give you praise. You are the same
every day.
We worship you, Jesus. We thank you, Father. We bless your name,
Jesus. You're such a good and a faithful God.
We welcome you in this place tonight.
[music]
>> [singing] >> I simple melodies [singing] of sacrifice.
Open hands and open [music and singing] hearts. You're the only one I want.
Treasure my [singing] delight.
like
Holy [music] Spirit [singing] fall like gra Holy
[music and singing] Spirit have your way. Let [singing] your
glory fall down. Let your glory fall [music] down.
thing I ask, I seek so [music and singing] much more than anything to
dwell within your house for all [music and singing] my days.
Lord, knowing you is [music and singing] everything. So I let go of lesser
things. You alone are [singing] worthy [music] of my praise.
So stir in [singing] me a passion for your name.
All [singing] I pray Holy [music] Spirit fall
I pray. Holy [music and singing] Spirit have your
way. Let your glory [singing and music] fall down. Let your glory
fall down.
Fall. [singing] [music]
Holy Spirit. Fall. [music and singing]
Holy [music and singing] Spirit. Have your way. Let
[singing] your glory [music] fall down. Let your glory [singing] fall [music]
down.
Have your way. Have your [music] way. [singing]
May I never lose the wonder of your [singing] presence. [music] May
I always stand in awe of who you are.
Oh, the beauty and [music] the gift of your friendship
is unlike anything I've ever known. [music and singing] May I never May I
never lose the water [singing] of the [music] resence. We always
stand and [singing] above who you are. [music]
Oh, the [singing] beauty and the gift [music] of the over
like [music] anything I've ever known so far. [music and singing]
Oh, Holy Spirit. Holy [music] Spirit fall [singing]
away. Holy Spirit [music] of you. [singing]
Let your [music] glory fall down. Let your [singing] glory fall.
[music] Oh my. [singing]
Holy Spirit [music] pour
come and have your way. Have you
[music and singing] let your glory forever
[music]
lose the wonder [music] of [singing] your words?
[singing]
All the beautiful [music]
gift [music and singing] your gra
[music]
[music] [singing] your presence I always stand of who you
of the beauty and the [music] gift of [singing] your presence
unlike anything [music] I've ever known.
All [music and singing] I pray, Holy [singing] Spirit,
I pray, Holy [singing] Spirit, [music] have your
way. Let [singing] your glory [music] fall down. Let your glory
fall down. Let it fall. >> [music and singing]
>> Let it fall. [singing]
Come on, let's lift our hands and we [music] press into [singing]
his presence. Oh, we turn our attention to you, Jesus. [music] May
we never forget. [singing] May we never forget.
You are the one true living God. [music]
Oh, we bless your name. [music]
We bless your name. >> Praise your name. >> We bless [singing] your name.
We bless your name. [music]
>> [singing]
>> like rain.
Come on, church. Let's just press in for just another minute. [music]
Just lift your hands, lift your [singing] voices. Oh, we thank you,
Lord.
[singing] >> [music]
[singing] [music] >> We praise you.
[singing]
[music] Oh, we bless your name. We give
you praise. [singing and music]
We thank you, Father. We thank you, Father. >> Thank you, Jesus. >> We
thank you, Jes. >> Oh, let's just lift up our hands right now
and thank him. Let's just thank him for being a good God.
Thank him for his glory. Thank him for his goodness. Thank him
for his power. Thank him for the fact that you're here tonight.
[music] >> That he's kept you your entire life. >> Thank you, Lord,
>> that we live in this amazing country where we can worship you
freely. Oh, thank you, [music] Lord. Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord.
You know, there's just nothing like being in the presence of God.
There's just nothing like it. There's nothing comparable.
You know, when Moses went up on that mountain, I I I
think I mentioned this a few Sundays ago. Moses went up on
Mount Si and he got the Ten Commandments. And the Bible says
that he was up there a long time. And when he came
down, he was literally glowing in the glory of God. They could
see something was different about Moses. It was like his entire countenance
had changed. It was different. Let me tell you, you can't be
in God's presence and stay the way you are. Can you imagine
being on that mountain with God? Just you and him. Just you
and him having a conversation. But you know, you can have that
same relationship. Matter of fact, you can have a better relationship because
that same God who was up on that mountain with Moses 40
days and 40 nights, that same God who was speaking to Moses,
writing the Ten Commandments out with his finger on tablets of stone.
That same God dwells on the inside of you. That same God
wants to have a relationship with you and I. He's a personable
God. And in the Old Testament, he wasn't able to have as
close a relationship as he wanted. But now, there's nothing that can
block it. There's nothing that can hinder. There's no sin. There's no
problem. There's no shame. Nothing. And once you're born again, he comes
to live on the inside of you. And he can have a
close, intimate relationship with you if you want it. It's not
up to God. Hey, it's not up to God if you read
your Bible. It's not up to God if you spend time praying.
Does God want you to do these things? Absolutely. But just like
you do in a marriage relationship with or with a boyfriend or
a girlfriend, the more time you spend with them, the more your
relationship begins to develop. What about the less time you spend? Well,
you don't know him that well, right? This is one of the biggest
problems we have as Christians. We don't know God very well. And
he's a God that's not a far off. He's a God that's
close and the Bible says he inhabits the praises of his people.
He loves it when we do what we just did tonight and
worship him. But you know, you don't have to wait for a
church service to worship God. You can worship him in your car.
You can worship him in the shower. That's when you'll sing the
best. You'll be you'll be in the shower worshiping God thinking, "Man,
I should try out for the worship team." And then you get
out and your your wife is like, "No, you shouldn't cry out
for the worship team." There's something about the acoustics of that, you
sound better than you do. Amen. You can worship him anywhere. God
loves it when we worship him. He's done so much for us.
The least we can do is give him thanks. The least we
can do is worship him. Amen. Amen. Praise God. Well, [music] you
guys can be seated tonight. Is anybody excited to be here tonight?
Healing and miracle night at Movement Church. We got any hungry people
in the room tonight? Any hungry people in the room? I'm not
talking about physically hungry. You may not have eaten supper yet, but
I'm talking about being hungry for the word. I know if you're
here on a Wednesday night, you're hungry for the word. Amen. I
want to share with you just for a few minutes, and then
we're going to pray for some people, lay hands on some people.
But I want to share with you just for a few minutes
some things that the Lord has been dealing with me. Some things
the Lord has been putting on my heart. Um and and there's
a lot Thank you. a lot of things to do with healing.
But let me just say this. I I've shared this before, but
uh several months ago I had some Jehovah's No, it wasn't Jehovah's
Witness. It was uh Mormons come to the front door of our
house. I got to spend some quality time really talking with them
and sharing Jesus with them and and all of that. And you
know, it was real interesting. I really had a revelation that day.
I was really asking the Lord because I really wanted to help
them. I really wanted to minister to them. And I I I
reached a point where I saw that there was nothing else that
could be done. There was nothing else that could be said. There
was nothing else I could do to convince them that that what
they were doing wasn't aligned with scripture. And that wasn't scripture over
there, by the way. That little other book you're holding is not
scripture. That's not the word of God. And I and I and
I just had a revelation and I was just like, "We've reached
an impath, right? They don't believe the Bible. I don't believe the
Book of Mormon. How are we ever going to resolve this?" And
the Lord and I and I as we as I left and
and they left and and they finally just, you know, broke away
from me. The the and they put us on a list. Haley
was telling me that she they approached her the other day and
and said she goes to movement church and they they bolted really
fast. [laughter]
So, I guess we're a blacklisted now, maybe. Amen. But anyway, I
was I was just praying about it like, Lord, how can we
ever reach them? Because it's not a logical argument that we can
we can make. And the Lord began to talk to me about
the power of the Holy Spirit and began to talk to me
about how this is why you need miracles in your life. This
is why you need the power of God in your life. Because
yeah, you can argue all day about f uh the concepts of
the word and different scriptures, but nobody can argue with the power
of God. When the power of God is present, when the power
of God manifests, you just can't argue with it. Somebody was sick
and now they're healed. Somebody was missing something in their life and
now it's fixed. Somebody was broken and now they're no longer broken.
When the manifested power and presence of God shows up, it changes
their life and it will change the way they think. Amen. >> Christians
need the power. I refuse to be without the power of God.
I refuse to do what I do as a pastor without the
power of God. If I don't have the supernatural power, I don't
want to do anything. I don't want to preach. I don't want
to lay hands on people. I don't want to do anything. It's
not just a philosophical argument that we make. It's not just words
on a page. These words are full of power. >> You and I
are full of power. So tonight, what I want to share with
you is is what this power is, where it comes from, and
I I want to share a little bit about how we receive
this healing and when we can have it. 2 Corinthians chapter 5:E1
17, it says, "Therefore, as any if anyone is in Christ, he
is a new creation. Old things have passed away. Behold, all things
have become new. What I want you to see tonight and focus
on is the fact that salvation begins as soon as you're born
again. Salvation begins as soon as you accept Jesus as your savior.
Why am I saying this? I'm saying this because there are many
Christians and there's a popular thought process that that when you get
born again, the ultimate goal is for you to go to heaven.
And being saved is all about going to heaven. Now, let me
tell you, go heaven's an amazing place. We're going there. Okay? Heaven's
an amazing place. We're going there. All of our loved ones that
are born again before us are there waiting for us. It will
be bigger and awesome, if that's a word, than you've ever dreamed.
Okay? I am not minimizing at all going to heaven. I look
forward one day to going to heaven in about 50 years. I'm
serious. I'm planning on being here at least 100 years. Amen. If you
don't start amening maybe 99. No, I'm kidding. But heaven's going to
be an awesome place. But you don't have to wait till you
get to heaven to experience salvation.
Amen. You don't have to wait till you get to heaven to
experience the blessings of salvation because salvation begins now when you're born
again now. Amen. Let me ask you, are you saved tonight? >> Okay.
So, so you're already saved. Salvation begins now. And the benefits of
your salvation begin now. You know, when you go to work for
somebody, you go to work for a company, when do the benefits
start? As soon as you sign and say, "I'm a part of
this company. I signed my name. I'm now part of this company.
I'm going to go to work for you." The benefits start immediately,
right? They should start immediately depending on the company, but you you
should have uh benefits associated with you as being a part of
that company. God is not different. He's not making you wait 40,
50 years for you to have benefits. Yes, one day we're going
to heaven, but salvation is for today. And salvation is a big
word. It is a multiaceted word. The the Greek word is sooo.
That's the root word for salvation. And it means being made whole
in your spirit, soul, and body. Restored to health. Let me just
read it to you. The definition here. Restored to health to deliver,
to rescue you from danger, to make you whole, and to heal
you. So, it's really not a question whether or not healing is
a part of salvation. It's in the definition. Now, some people will
even argue with that, right? They'll be like, "Well, I don't know if
healing is for today. I don't know if healing is a part of
salvation." The definition says it is. And this is not just a
random de uh this is right out of Strong's concordance, one of
the most popular, well-defined uh concordance it that's ever been made. Strong's
concordance says that salvation so includes healing. So it's not really a
question. Not too many people, some will, but not too many people
will question whether healing is for you. The question is where is
that healing? Where do I find that healing? Yeah, God heals people
when he sends them to heaven. A lot of people believe that
and they'll say, "Yeah, healing is available and one day we'll be
healed when we get to heaven." Let me tell you something that
is not true for the one. Amen. It's not.
Let me tell you something. When just just ask ourselves a question,
okay? When people approached Jesus and they needed healing in their body,
how did Jesus respond? Did Jesus would they come up to Jesus
and then they're a leopard and say, "I know you can heal
me, but I don't know if you will." And Jesus says, "I
will." He draws a sword. Just hang on a second. Whack. Going
to heaven and you'll be healed. Oh, you need healing in your
body? All right. Well, hang on. I'm going to push some horrible
disease and sickness on you so in two months you'll be dead
and then you'll be healed. But that's exactly what many people believe.
Many people believe that you'll get healed when you're in heaven. Let
me tell you tonight, there's nothing to be healed from in heaven.
There's nothing to be healed from. There's no sickness there. Of course,
there's no You're healed in heaven because there's no sickness in heaven
to be healed from. When when you leave your body one day,
what happens to your body? Your body is here on this earth
that you don't take it with you. It's we put it in
the ground and we have a memorial service for you. Your body
STAYS HERE. YOUR BODY MUST not have gotten healed if it was
a sickness or disease that took you out. Well, they're healed in
heaven, but their body's still here and their body didn't get healed.
You see the difference? But I'm here to tell you tonight that
salvation includes healing. And you don't have to wait till you get
to heaven to experience salvation and all the benefits of it because
healing is available today. Amen. >> So, where does this healing come from?
How how is it that we have healing on this earth today?
Well, let's read this out of Luke chapter 4 verse number 18
says, "The spirit of the Lord is upon me because he has
anointed me to preach the gospel to the poor. He has sent
me to heal the brokenhearted, to proclaim liberty to the captives and
recovery of sight to the blind, to set at liberty those who
are oppressed." So Jesus said this. Jesus said, "The spirit of the
Lord is upon me. He's anointed me." Now let's ask OURSELVES A
QUESTION. WHY DOES JESUS NEED TO BE ANOINTED?
Why does he need to be anointed? I mean, is Jesus, Most
people believe, this is another popular belief in Christian circles, that Jesus
healed because he was Jesus. Well, he was Jesus, so he could
heal people. No, he couldn't. He couldn't heal anybody until he was
anointed by the Holy Spirit. And once he was anointed by the
Holy Spirit, he proclaimed it. He found, the Bible says, he opened
the the scroll of Isaiah and he found the place where it
was written. Ah, there I am. The spirit of the Lord is
upon me. He has anointed me. What has he anointed me to
do? He anointed me to preach the gospel to the poor. He's
anointed me to heal the brokenhearted, set at liberty though the to
the captives, recovery of sight to the blind. He's anointed me to
do this. I am anointed to do this. How is healing happening
now on the earth? Because there's an anointed man going around healing
everybody. There's a man who's been anointed by the Holy Spirit healing
everybody. And everywhere he went, he's healing people. And he wasn't healing
them by killing them so he could send them to heaven. Come
on, somebody. He wasn't hurt. He wasn't putting sickness on them so
he could heal them. That's another one people say, "Well, you know,
God God tears you down so he can bring you up." No,
he doesn't. If he did, show me scripture where Jesus did that.
Show me scripture where I'm gonna come to Jesus and he's like,
"Okay, I I'm gonna tear you down so I can lift you
up. I'm g I'm gonna break you snap in two and I'm
gonna make you broken and miserable so you have to come to
me and you have to worship me." That's not true. If it
were true, there would be scripture supporting that idea. But I'm here
to tell you, so many people believe that. So many people believe
that God's going to break you. God's got to he's got to
break you down and and just break you down so he can
lift you back up. That's not the God we serve. Jesus wasn't
anointed to hurt you. He was anointed to heal you. And that
anointing, he said, "The spirit of the Lord is upon me. He
has anointed me." Jesus was anointed by the Holy Spirit. And guess
what? You and I are anointed by the same Holy Spirit. You
and I have the same Holy Spirit. And you and I, if
you've been baptized in the Holy Spirit, are anointed with the same
Holy Spirit because Jesus said when he ascended unto heaven, the last
thing he said to his disciples, do you think this was important?
I mean, if someone was going to go away for a long
period of time and they were going to be gone for uh
couple thousand years and but yet they're going to tell you something
before they leave, what they're going to tell you. How many you
know that they weren't just talking about the food they ate. That
was good pizza last night. Yeah, good pizza. Yeah, it was great.
Great restaurant. All right, we'll see y'all later. Couple thousand years. We'll
see you later. No, he was talking about very, very important things.
And in Acts chapter one, we get a glimpse. We get we
get from Jesus mouth himself how this healing is going to take
place now that he's leaving now that he's leaving this earth. Acts
chapter 1 verse8 he said but you shall receive power when the
Holy Spirit has come upon you. So Jesus said the spirit of
the Lord is upon me. He has anointed me. But now he's
talking about the Holy Spirit coming upon you. Now there are two
different things here. You've got the Holy Spirit on the inside of
you when you're born again. You've got an anointing on the inside
of you. The spirit of God lives on the inside of you.
These people were born again. But now he's talking about another experience
with the Holy Spirit where literally you can be baptized in the
Holy Spirit and have the Holy Spirit not just living on the
inside of you but covering all over you. And the Bible says
that the Holy Spirit ascended or descended from heaven and it looked
like fire coming from heaven and the fire came down on each
one of them and they were all baptized in the Holy Spirit.
They began to speak with other tongues. You lose a lot of
people when you mention that. I don't know why. I I think
it's because the devil has fought so hard to stop you from
operating under the anointing. He's fought so hard to prevent Christians from
taking that next step that God wants you to take. BECAUSE LET
ME TELL YOU, HE wants you walking around this earth just like
Jesus did. He wants you walking around healing people. He wants you
walking around laying hands on people. Is that not what he told
us to do? That that's why the devil has fought this so
hard is because he's oh, we get hung up on the tongue
thing. Stop getting hung up on the tongue thing. Yes, you get
to speak in the heavenly prayer language and that's awesome. But you
forget what Jesus said. YOU'RE GOING TO GET POWER WHEN YOU DO.
And this power we know is dunamis power. This is God's miracle
working power. So what we're saying is when you're anointed by the
Holy Spirit and this power comes on you now you are the
ones that are to take healing and deliverance and open blind eyes
and set captives free to all the earth. >> Jesus is not going
to be here physically walking the earth anymore. It's on us now.
It's on you and I. We're the next ones. And the question
for for for year after year after this for for for century
after century is who's going to step up? Who's going to step
up? Who's going to actually believe what Jesus said? Now, you'll find
a lot of theologians that will completely cut this up and and
try to explain away why this is not for today. You'll have
a lot of people try to explain away why this power is
not for today. And we just wish God would. We hope he
would. So then they start developing other doctrine which says he breaks
you and smacks you down because and sometimes Jesus will heal you
and sometimes he won't. That's all a bunch of hoie.
Why? Because they they don't embrace the power of God. And when
you don't have the power of God, none of these other things
will even be possible. So we got to explain them away. But
we're talking about how you can walk in and operate in this
power. Jesus said that we could operate in this power and be
his witnesses in Jerusalem, Judea, Samaria, and to the ends of the
earth. Like Salana, Texas, like McKini, like Aubrey, like Dallas. Wherever
you go, you take the power with you. Why? Because you're anointed.
You've been anointed by God. You have this power on you. Now,
Paul had the power. I won't get into all the scriptures tonight,
but you know, there's there's been people over the years, it's kind
of funny. There's been people over the years uh I want to
do exactly what Paul did and things like that. And I remember
one account in scripture, they they were just taking handkerchiefs, remember? And
and Paul was just putting his hands on them and they would
take these handkerchiefs that Paul just put his hands on and they
would put them on people and those people would be healed. Demons
would come at them because the handkerchief got put on them. So
I had someone come to me one time said, "Pastor, we got
to get the handkerchiefs out. We got to get the handkerchiefs out.
It's so easy to focus on the wrong thing. It wasn't the
hanky or the snot that was on it. Can I just be
real blunt? Too late. I was It wasn't the handkerchief. It was
the anointing on the Apostle Paul's life. And that anointing, listen to
me, that anointing can be transferred from one to another.
That anointing is supposed to be transferred from one person to another
person. It's supposed to. Remember when Jesus was walking along? Famous story.
We talked about it so many times, but it's good to hear
it again. He's walking along and the woman with issue of blood,
been sick for 12 years, comes up behind Jesus and just touched
the hem of his garment. Didn't even touch his skin. Touched the
hem of his garment, the cloth of his garment. And and the
Bible says that virtue better translation would be power came out of
him because it was dunamis that said to come out of him.
Power came out of him. Why? Jesus was anointed and when she
touched in faith his garment, that anointing that was on him flew
out of him and into her. And Jesus said he felt it
happen. And that's why he stopped. He could feel that anointing going
into somebody else. Oh, praise God. We need to know about the
anointing. We need to operate under the anointing. We need to embrace
the supernatural power of God and do exactly what Jesus said. We've
got a whole world to reach, guys. We've got a whole world
that's dying and hurting. And they need to see something besides religion.
They need to see something besides us just quote scripture. They need
to see somebody walking on this earth that's anointed. Remember when Jesus
was in the storm and the boat was sinking and he got
up and he rebuked the wind and the waves AND THEY SAID,
"WHAT KIND OF A MAN IS THIS?" There's an answer to that
question. The answer to the question that they asked, nobody answered it
in the Bible. It was just them. They're like, "What kind of
a man is this?" It was a man anointed by the Holy
Spirit. And let me tell you something. There is a man that
pastors movement church that's anointed by the Holy Spirit. But guess what?
I'm not the only one. It's not just for pastors. Praise God.
It's for me, too. I'm thankful. Well, you're just aware. No. I
I'm TELLING YOU TODAY THAT YOU ARE anointed by the Holy Spirit.
When the when the Holy Spirit comes upon you and you're baptized
in the Holy Spirit, YOU'RE ANOINTED AS WELL TO DO WHAT? THE
EXACT SAME thing that Jesus did. Because what the anointing is on
you. The anointing does what it does. The Bible says it removes
burdens from people's lives and it destroys yolks in their life. We're
not talking about egg yolk now. We're talking about bondage that the
enemy has put on you. We're talking about sickness and disease. We're
talking about anything that's happened to you as a result of being
on this planet that God did not want to happen. Let me
tell you, the anointing will break it. Amen. So, that anointing is
on us. This is how people get healed today. It's because of
the anointing. It's not the handkerchief. Ah, goodness. We get hung up
on on that. I'll show you another one we get hung up
on. Look at this one. James 5:14. Is anyone among you sick?
Let him call on the doctor. No, no, no. That's not what
it says.
Boy, it gets quiet when I start picking on this one, isn't
it? Isn't that the first thing most people do today? Born again,
spiritfilled, anointed of God will call the doctor first. YOU SHOULD CALL
the elders of the church first and say, "Pray with me right
now that this junk will leave my body." And you can even
do it. You can still go to the doctor. I'm not, no
one's mad at you for going to the doctor. There's nothing wrong
with going to the doctor, but the Bible says, I mean, believe
what the Bible says. The See, when we get this out of
here, here's the thing. Oh my goodness.
Prayer and asking for prayer from the leaders of the church should
not be the last resort. Well, we've done everything else. We've done
everything else we can. I guess I'm going to go see if
someone can pray for me now. You get the picture. That should
be the first thing that we do when something, hey, agree with
me in prayer. I know this doesn't belong to me. I plan
on go seeing a doctor if I still have it next week.
But praise God, I know the covenant promises I have in the
word. And when we agree together, we can rebuke. And that anoint
rebuke whatever that is. And that anointing will remove that burden from
your life. So many Christians will get healed first before they even
have to go to the doctor. You'll save money. Oh, I got your
attention now, didn't I? You'll save money. Amen. So, it says, "If
anybody is among you sick," he's talking to the church. Let him
call for the elders of the church and let them pray over
him. Listen to this. Anointing him with oil in the name of
the Lord. Anointing them. Well, we are the anointed ones and we
are the ones doing the anointing. Did you catch that part? We
are the anointed ones now. And we are the ones with the
anointing on us to anoint someone else with what? The anointing.
What is that? It's the power. It's the dunamis. And the Bible
says that when we do that, that anointing that's on us, now
here's what's happened. Here's what's happened. People get stuck on the oil.
Well, pastor, go get the vial of Where's the vial of oil?
Well, I got some oil. But the anointing is not in the
oil. It's symbolic. [laughter] I think this is funny.
The anointing was It wasn't the hanky. It wasn't the oil. It
was the anointing on it. It was the fact that we are
anointed. That's why the handkerchief was anointed. It wasn't someone and had
someone, you know, they try to do all these handkerchief things and
dip them in all kinds of spices and they smell good and
all. Okay, great. But that's not going to get the job done.
People have over complicated this healing thing so bad and they try
to figure it out. Oh, we just got to figure this out.
HOW DID PAUL DO THIS? HOW DID HE DO THIS? What kind
of hanky was it? Did it have little frilly things on the
side? Did he use it before he handed it out and prayed
over it? Oh, praise God. No. Oh, no. No. No. No. Please.
No. Was it even a handkerchief or was it just a piece
of cloth? What kind of cloth was it? What color was it?
See, we get h we get hung up on all the wrong
thing. The point being is it was the anointing transferred to that
cloth. It was the anointing flowing through Jesus body into his clothes.
into that woman with the issue of blood. It's the anointing right
here flowing from the elders of the church into somebody. And look
what the very next verse says. And the prayer of faith will
so save the sick and the Lord will raise him up and
if he has committed sins, he will be forgiven. Did you hear
what I just read? And the prayer of faith will save the
sick. So when we anoint someone with oil and we pray the
prayer of faith on them, what's the Bible say it's going to
happen? It's not a trick question. The prayer of faith will save
the sick. So he said, if you're sick, call on the elders
of the church. They will lay their hands on you, anoint you
with oil, and they'll pray the prayer of faith on you. Not
the prayer of doubt and unbelief over you. Not the prayer. Boy,
I hope this works. Well, I don't know what kind what you
say you had. Oh, have you been to the doctor yet? Oh,
I'm I'm I'm pointing the finger at ministers, too. How many ministers
will first ask, "Have you been to the doctor?" You know, Jesus
never asked that question. Guy with leprosy, been full of leprosy. Have
you been to the doctor? What did he say? How bad is
it? How how many how many weeks you got left to live?
Pressure, pressure, pressure. Why? Because then you're looking at your own strength
and your own ability. Let me tell you, none of those things
matter. Let me say it again. None of those things matter. The
kind of sickness it is, how long you've had it, none. Did
it matter to Jesus? Was he like, "Oh, no. How long have
you been sick? Oh, no. What do you have?" None of those
things mattered. Why? Because the anointing doesn't care. The anointing is
more powerful than whatever it is that you got.
True. It's the anointing. It's the anointing. It's the supernatural power. That
anointing that's on us is more powerful than the sickness that's in
your body or the pain that you're experiencing or whatever it is.
The anointing is more powerful. God's power is greater than that. And
when you believe that and we pray for you, the prayer of
faith, that's believing it. The Bible says the prayer of faith will
save the sick. That's exactly what we're going to do tonight. If
anybody has sickness in their body and you want us to pray
for you, we're going to do exactly what the Bible says. We're
going to I'm telling you right now, my hands are anointed right
now. We're already anointed. Well, you're gonna get the good oil from
from Israel. I'm serious, guys. People get so not against the oil
from Israel, but don't get hung up on the oil or the
handkerchief or the method or it's the anointing. I said it's the
anointing. You and I are anointed. How How is this healing going
to take place on the earth if there's no anointing here? How
would it ever take place? Jesus said, "It's here. The spirit of
the Lord is upon me. He's anointed me to go do everything
that I'm doing." And you know, Most Bible scholars believe he prayed
that prayer everywhere he went. He would go in the synagogue and
say the spirit, that's how he started every single service that he
started in every single city. The spirit of the Lord is upon
me. He has anointed me. It was huge. It was big. He
announced it from the beginning. And I'm announcing it tonight. The spirit
of the Lord is upon us. He has anointed us with what?
The same power that raises the dead. The same power that cures
cancer. The same power that heals sickness and disease. The same power
that'll cure any issue that you're having tonight. Let me tell you
something. God wants every person here tonight healed. How do I know
that? Because his word says he desires that all men be saved
and come to the knowledge of him. And that word saved is
the word so. That means not just salvation going to heaven. It
means healing. And it starts now. I said it starts now. It
starts right now. If you have sickness in your body, I want
you to come forward right now. If you got pain in your
body, if you're having any kind of physical problems, mental problems, thank
you, Lord.
Thank you, Lord, for the anointing. Thank you, Lord, for the anointing.
Let's just be praying right now, listening to the Holy Spirit. Let's
listen to his voice.
Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Jesus.
Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord.
What can we pray with you?
Ringing.
Yeah. Acting up.
Well, the devil's getting on your nerves. That's what I just heard.
So, we're going to get the devil off your nerves in the
name of Jesus and the anointing that's on our life. We declare
right now, nerves, you function properly. Devil, you get off her nerves
right now in Jesus name. Nerves, you function properly in the name
of Jesus. Will not have this. She's a child of the king.
We pray and agree right now. the prayer of faith, believing, trusting
you, Lord, as the healer. And that anointing right now is flowing
into her body, healing what's been broken, uh, putting together, what's been
disconnected. Thank you, Lord, that she does not have to have this
the rest of her life. I don't care what others have said.
The answer is no. God says, "No, you don't have to have
this. The world says you do." The world says, "Oh, it's just
a part of Bell's policy. Oh, it's just a part of this."
But you've been redeemed from the curse of the law. That doesn't
apply to you. Thank you, Lord, for healing right now in the
name of Jesus. Every nerve, every nerve functioning properly in the name
of Jesus. Thank you, Father. Yes, ma'am.
Oh, put your hand right there on her chest. In the name
of Jesus, we rebuke that crud. We pray the prayer of faith
over her right now. Healing, wholeness over her lungs, clear lungs in
the name of Jesus Christ of Nazareth. Thank you, Lord, for that
anointing right now flowing into her body. The spirit of the Lord
is upon us. We are anointed for this purpose to lay hands
on the sick. And the sick, you have no choice. You have
to recover in the name of Jesus. Lungs, you have to be
clear right now in Jesus name. Oh, just take a deep breath.
Take a deep breath. Thank you, Lord, for clear lungs in the
name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord. Clear lungs in
the name of I'm glad you came forward because the Lord told
me to pray for you tonight. You weren't coming forward. I was
calling you out, girl. Thank you, Lord.
Yes. Yes. Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord. Lay your hands on
her back. Father, in the name of Jesus, we come into agreement
right now. Thank you, Lord, for the anointing. Thank you, Lord, for
the anointing. Oh, the spirit of the Lord is upon us. We
are anointed. You got a bunch of anointed hands laying on you
right now. Back, you line up in Jesus name. Body, you recover
in Jesus name. Oh, I I just see uh the enemy has
just been after you when your physical body and it and it
just seems like when one thing seems to come and go, then
something else is popping up. And and I and that the Lord
wants you to know that that is the enemy trying to distract
you, trying to bring you down. And it's time to take a
stand right now. And tonight you're taking that stand. And by faith
receive all. I said all. I said all of the anointing that's
needed to heal every aspect, every every symptom in the name of
Jesus. I rebuke that in her body in Jesus name. Back you
function properly. Pain you leave in the name of Jesus. From the
top of her head to the soles of her feet. And devil
you take your hand off of God's property [music] right now. You
take your hands off of her. She's a child of the most
high God. She's the temple of the Holy Spirit. And the same
spirit in her is the spirit that kicks your tail all over
this earth. That spirit is rising up on the inside of her.
Oh, thank you, Lord, that she becomes a dangerous person for the
enemy to try to attack. A dangerous person that the enemy says,
"You better leave." No, leave that one alone cuz she's dangerous. Oh,
she's going to she's going to come after us. She's going to
be saying things about us. How she's been healed, how she's been
delivered, how she no longer deals with those things any longer because
by Jesus stripes, she was healed. Thank you, Lord, for it. Thank
you for that anointing right now. It's flowing in your body right
now. I can feel my fingers tingling right now. The anointing is
coming in. Oh, it's healing everything. Everything that's out of alignment in
her body. Things on the inside. Oh, things on the inside are
being healed right now in the name of Jesus.
You don't have to be guilty about anything. You don't have to
say, "Oh, I ate this, so I going to have to have
that." Absolutely not. You don't have to have any of that junk.
You don't have to [music] accept any of that curse because you
are redeemed from it in Jesus name. Thank you father. Thank you
Lord. >> Yes. >> Yes. Yes.
Yeah.
>> Thank you Lord.
Well, you know, there was a time when Jesus healed people that
weren't present. Actually, there was multiple times where he did that with
a centurion servant. He said, "I'll come heal your servant." And what
did what did the centurion say? He said, "You don't have to
come. Just speak the word. Just speak the word." We're going to
speak some words tonight. We're going to speak some words. Thank you
for standing in. Father, in the name of Jesus, we speak to
that inflammation in Caleb's mouth right now in the name of Jesus.
Thank you, Lord. He does not have [music] to have this. Oh,
I see this as a sign in his life. Oh, thank you,
Lord, that right now that healing power is going into his body,
mouth, you be restored in the name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord.
And there'll be no other explanation. Oh, no. the the the way
it was done, the way it happened, there'll be no one [music]
to get credit but God almighty. Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord.
We speak to that mouth right now in Jesus name. Be healed
in Jesus name. Oh, thank you, Father.
And he'll and I and I just see this. He'll say he'll
give glory to God without even realizing he did it. He'll be
like, "Whoa, I didn't know I said that." But he'll give glory
to God. It'll just come slipping out of his mouth. Just come
right out of his spirit. He'll give glory to God for it.
Thank you, Lord. He's healed by Jesus stripes. >> Thank you, Lord. >> Thank
you, Jesus, for that anointing flowing in his mouth right now in
Jesus name. Restoring in Jesus name. Thank you, Lord. And here's something
else I heard the Lord say. You know, everybody that Jesus healed
in the in all of his ministry, you know, they weren't perfect
people. None of them were even born again.
Let me tell you something. Nothing disqualifies you. Nothing.
Nothing disqualifies. Thank you, Lord. Praise you, Father. Thank you, Lord.
Pain gone. Pain from that kidney stone. Yeah. Yep. Father, in the
name of Jesus, as we lay hands on her, we do exactly
what you said. The anointing oil right now is flowing in her
body. Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord. Pain you leave right now
in Jesus name. Oh, kidney stone, you're rebuked in her body. Anything
remaining, anything trying to form, I rebuke it in the name of
Jesus. We come into agreement with Crystal right now. I thank you,
Lord, that that anointing is flowing in her body right now. Healing
what has been damaged. Oh, restoring what's been damaged in the name
of Jesus. Oh, this is nothing but a silly little distraction. Just
a silly little distraction. And in the name of Jesus, we call
this finished, done, over in the name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord,
for that anointing. Thank you right now. Right now, in the name
of Jesus. The spirit of the Lord is upon you. He's anointed
you. And that anointing removes burdens. This is a burden. This is
a burden. I rebuke that in Jesus name. I rebuke [music] that
burden. Tell it to leave and anointing. You do what you do.
Set her free in Jesus name. Thank you, Lord. Yes, ma'am.
Let's pray for you. Okay, we lay hands on you and pray
for you. Thank you, Father. Oh, for the childlike faith. Oh, you
said in your word, you said, "Oh, keep them away. Keep them
away." And no, Jesus, you said, "Bring them in. Bring them in."
Thank you Lord for that healing power. Thank you Lord for removing
that itch in the name of Jesus. Restoring her skin, restoring her
body. Oh, I thank you Lord for that anointing right now in
the name of Jesus. Even at her age, she's experiencing it. This
is the normal. This is normal. This is just the norm. Thank
you, Father, for that anointing removing this itch in Jesus name. And
we just speak wholeness over her body in the name of Jesus.
This will not be a lingering thing. This thing ends [music] tonight
in the name of Jesus. Thank you Lord for the anointing. The
elders have laid hands on anointed her with the oil of the
Holy Spirit and body. You recover in Jesus name. We speak to
it. Say recover in the name of Jesus. Amen. Amen. Thank you
Lord. Praise you father.
busted your hand.
>> Oh man. >> Yes. >> Yes. >> Father, in the
name of Jesus, we thank you for that anointing. You said you
said that Josh could come forward tonight and call on prayer. The
prayer of faith you said will save the sick. We are to
anoint him with oil right now. The oil is flowing in his
arm right now in his hand. Oh, restoring what's been messed up.
Oh, the nerves and the tendons. Oh, anything out of alignment. Anything
that's off, anything that's broken, we speak restoration over it right now
[music] in the name of Jesus. Thank you for the anointing. Thank
you for that anointing flowing in his hand right now. The power
is flowing right now. Oh, it's flowing right now in the name
of Jesus. things that he couldn't do now he'll be able to
do. Thank you Lord. We call his hand restored in the name
of Jesus. >> Restoration, wholeness, >> healing in the name.
>> In the name of Jesus. Thank you Lord. Thank you Lord. >> Were
you able to bend it before?
>> Praise God. Thank you Lord. >> Well that seems to be working. Praise
God. Thank you, Lord. >> Thank you, Jesus. >> Thank you, Lord. Praise. Let's
just praise him for a minute. Let's just praise him for a
minute. Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord. Jesus, for being our healer.
Thank you, Lord. Pastor Chris is not the healer. Jesus is the
healer. But Jesus has anointed us. He's empowered us to lay hands
on broken hands, broken bodies, sickness, and disease. And sickness,
disease, and broken hands have to bow their knee to the anointing
of the Holy One of Israel, Jesus Christ, the anointed one. Thank
you, Father. Thank you, Jesus. I'm stirred up. Thank you, Lord. Praise
God. Did you need prayer?
Oh, his tongue. Yeah, he told me earlier he bit his tongue
earlier. [music] Father, in the name of Jesus. Oh, thank you, Father,
for restoring his tongue. Oh, that pain that Oh, we we've all
experienced it. Every single one of us have experienced pain. We we
bite our tongue. And so, I thank you, Lord, for restoration in
his tongue in Jesus name. I rebuke the pain right now in
the name of Jesus. The spirit of the Lord is upon us.
You have anointed us and that anointing is flowing in his body
right now in the name of Jesus. We thank you for it.
We praise you for it in Jesus name. Amen. Amen. Thank you
Lord. How's your tongue feeling?
You feeling better too? Praise God. Thank you Lord. >> Yes ma'am.
>> Your leg. Which leg is it? Well, let me just get down
here and we're just going to lay hands on your leg. And
when we lay hands on your leg, the power of God is
[music] going to come into your leg. Okay? Father, in the name
of Jesus, we rebuke this pain in Jesus name. Thank you, Lord.
Her leg is restored. Whatever the source of this pain is, we
don't even have to know what it is. It could just be
a bruise. It just could be something else. Doesn't matter. Leg be
restored in the name of Jesus. The spirit of the Lord is
upon us. You have anointed us. >> That anointing right now is flowing
in her leg in Jesus name. Restoring and removing the pain. Pain
you be gone in Jesus name. You leave her body in the
name of Jesus. Thank you Lord. Praise you. Now you can run
and jump and play.
Thank you Lord. Praise God. >> His tummy. >> Okay. Well, let's pray for
his tummy. Father, in the name of Jesus, we do exactly what
you said in your word. You said the spirit of the Lord
is upon us. You've anointed us. Thank you, Lord, for that anointing.
Thank you, Lord. That anointing right now is healing his tummy in
Jesus name. Tummy, you line up. You function properly in the name
of Jesus. That anointing right now is healing his stomach. Stomach ache,
you leave his body, you don't belong there. You leave. He's a
child of the most high God. You have no right to him
in the name of Jesus. And we rebuke this attack on his
body [music] in Jesus name. Amen. Amen. Thank you Lord. Praise God.
Thank you Lord. Thank you Lord. Who wants to stand in for
Jada? Kim, you look like Jada. You're here in front of me.
Jada was having some health issues. Jamie and Jasmine's little girl's having
some health issues this morning. And so she had to go uh
to the to the ER actually this morning. And so uh I
just want you to stand in for her because you know what?
The anointing has no distance limitations. There are no distance in the
spirit. So, Father, in the name of Jesus, as I lay my
head right now on Tim's head, thank you, Lord, that that anointing
is flowing in Jada's body in the name of Jesus. Oh, we
speak to her brain. >> You align in Jesus name. Things that are
off, you come back into balance in the name of Jesus. We
will not have this. We will not stand for it. We won't
Oh no. Oh no. Well, this is not happening in her body.
Oh, no. The the doctors have said, "Well, that's the way it's
going to be because it's hereditary." But the Lord says it's not.
>> The Lord says it's not hereditary. She's a child of the most
high. And that anointing right now is correcting everything that's out of
alignment in the name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord. Thank you for
the anointing. The spirit of the Lord is upon us. You've anointed
us. Thank you, Lord, for complete and total restoration in the name
of Jesus. Amen. And amen. Thank you, Lord. Praise you, Father. Yes,
ma'am. Yes, Jimmy.
>> Yes.
>> Thank you, Lord. >> Yes. Absolutely. She's standing in for her friend Jimmy
that's got heart issues in the name of Jesus as we lay
hands on Francesca tonight. Oh, thank you Lord that hands are being
laid right now on Jimmy. Oh, thank you Lord. You're the restorer.
The anointing restores. Thank you Lord for restoration in Jimmy's heart in
Jesus name. Thank put your hand right there on on where her
heart is. Thank you Lord for restoration right now in the name
of Jesus heart. We're speaking to you heart, you beat properly in
Jesus name. Heart, you be restored in the name of Jesus Christ
of Nazareth. The anointing is now touching you. The anointing is repairing
you. The anointing is causing you to be properly. You line up
in the name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord, for it. We call
it done in the name of Jesus. >> The spirit of the Lord
is upon us. You have anointed us. to do this to heal
hearts that are not working [music] properly. Broken hearts, but not just
in in emotional broken hearts, but physical hearts that are broken. I
thank you, Lord. His heart is restored. He gets a new heart.
Oh, thank you, Lord. It's like new. And the doctors will even
say, "It's like you got a new heart. It looks like the
old one, but you got a new one." And it's because of
the anointing. Thank you, Lord, for that anointing. restoring. Oh, and everything
that's been damaged because of his heart. Oh, any artery, any vein,
any any uh limb, any other symptoms that he's having, I rebuke
those in the name of Jesus. Thank you for that anointing from
the top of his head to the soles of his feet right
now. Restoring, restoring, restoring what the doctors say cannot be restored that
they say, "Oh, he'll have this problem the rest of his life."
We say no because of the anointing. It's restoring right now in
Jesus name. Thank you Lord for it. Praise you for Thank you
Lord. You you you talk to him. You tell him what we just
prayed tonight. >> Thank you Lord. Praise you father. That anointing is working
in his body in the name of Jesus. Praise you father. Let's
just thank you for a moment. Isn't God good? Let's just thank
him for a moment. Thank you Lord for the anointing. [music]
Let's pray in the spirit because the spirit of the Lord is
upon us. Let's just pray in the spirit.
Let's just sing in the spirit. Sing in the spirit tonight.
Thank you, Lord.
>> [music and singing] >> Let's just keep singing. Just keep singing for a moment.
[music] [singing]
[music]
>> [singing and music]
>> Owen, is it okay if I pray for you? >> Come up. I
want to lay hands on you and pray for you. Thank you,
Lord. >> I just felt impressed to pray for you. I don't know
what I'm praying over, but the spirit knows. Praise the Lord. Thank
you, Lord. Is there something or no? Don't even tell me. Thank
you, Lord. Father, in the name of Jesus, I pray for my
brother right now. Oh, the spirit of the Lord is upon us.
You've anointed us. He's anointed. Thank you for that anointing that's on
his life. Thank you, Father. Thank you, Lord, that he's protected and
he's kept in Jesus name. Oh, thank you, Lord. We rebuke any
attack from the enemy that would try to come after him and
convince him and change his mind about things. No, no, no. The
Lord says no. Thank you, Lord. You're a child of the most
high. You don't have to accept anything less than what God says
you are. What God says you can have. Thank you, Lord. And
I just feel in my spirit that there have been some things
that have been said about you, been spoken either to you or
about you that have kind of put some limits in your life.
And the Lord wanted me to tell you tonight, those limits don't
exist.
Those don't exist. Those limits are self-imposed limits. Thank you, Lord. There
are no limits. From God's perspective, there are no limits to what
you can do. He said you can do all things through Christ,
through the anointing that's on your life, strengthening you, empowering you. You
have value. You have purpose. Thank you, Lord. The enemy has has
tried to kind of work on you a little bit. Say, well,
you know, you're not much of [music] this or not much of
that. And he's really tried to belittle you a little bit. tried
to say, "Well, you're not this, you're not this kind of person."
And and you know, the Lord would say, "Stop listening to that
voice and stop playing the comparison game. He's anointed you in a
unique and special way." We're all unique and special. And don't let
the devil lie to you. Don't let the devil persuade you and
and try to tell you that you're not enough and that you
can't. The Lord says you can. You can what? You can do
all things through Christ strengthening you. Whatever it is he puts on
your heart to do. Whatever it is you stretch forth your hand
to do, the Lord says he'll make you prosper. You step out
in faith, you follow the leading of the Holy Spirit and you
do what he tells you to do and the Lord said I'm
when my hand is in it and you're following me, it'll prosper
and you'll be successful in all that you do. Be bold. Be
courageous in the name of Jesus. Thank you Lord. Thank you Lord
for boldness in Jesus name. Thank you Father. Does that bear witness
with your spirit? Thank you Lord. Praise you father. Thank you Lord.
Let's just pray in the spirit [music] for a minute. It's okay.
It's Wednesday night. We might as well hang out a while. Thank
you Lord. Thank you Lord. [singing]
depression. >> You're suffering from depression tonight. I want you to come forward
right now. [music and singing] >> You're suffering from depression. You've been depressed. Somebody here
has been depressed. You've been suffering from it. It may maybe it's
been a short-term thing. I don't know if it's short or long
term, but you've been suffering from depression. The Lord says healing [music]
night is not just for physical things. Healing not is for everything
that's been hindering you. Thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord. I heard the Lord say this.
You may not think it's been depression, but you've had thoughts that
have been belittling, be degrading thoughts, and you've been thinking about bad
things. And like, it's like these bad things have been rehearsing in
your mind. And the Lord said, "That's the seed of depression, anticipation
of evil, and you've been rehearsing these negative things in your mind."
And the Lord said, "Yeah, you don't recognize it's depression. That's why
you're not coming forward." But the Lord said, "The seed is there.
The seed has been planted of depression." And you need to deal
with that seed. You need to deal with it tonight. It needs
to be uprooted in the name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord. Thank
you, Lord. You've had bad thoughts, evil thoughts, just rehearsing over and
over in your mind. Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Jesus. We'll wait
just a minute. >> And I just heard the Lord say that. You
said, "Well, that's not me. I'm not a depressed person." But you've
been having these thoughts.
Those negative thoughts will lead to and grow depression in your mind.
And the Lord wants you free tonight. That's why he had me
say it. That's why you came tonight. Didn't even know you came
for it, but that's why you came to be set free. Thank
you, Jesus.
Thank you Lord. Thank you Lord. Let's just worship him. Let's worship
him.
>> Oh [music and singing] we bless your name. We bless your name.
[music] [singing]
Oh [music and singing] yeah, I'm a man. I'm a
>> Thank you. You know, it ought not be it ought not be
com uncomfortable for us to just worship in his presence. I think
so many times we get in [music] a hurry. We got to
do this or do that. But just spending time in his presence
listening. I want I want you to practice that right now. Just
listen. Listen to what he's saying. You might get answers to questions
you've had your entire life in the next two or three minutes
as we worship. Thank you. That's what I'm doing. I'm listening. I'm
listening for more instructions. >> Thank you, Lord. Just listen. Worship him and
listen in your heart. What is he telling you? What is he
saying?
He may give you a word to [music] share with everybody. Share
it. >> Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Jesus. [singing]
Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord. Grab this in the basket. Thank
you, Lord. >> I just had it in my heart that someone's got
a word. Jonathan. >> So, uh, something I saw today bore
witness with my spirit and I believe I should share it here
today. Uh, there was a man that Jesus approached and he asked
him a very simple question. He said, "Do you want to be
healed?" >> Do you want to be healed? And it it's simple in
theory, but the man had been there for years sitting there waiting
for the stirring of the waters. And many of you guys here
tonight, I believe the Lord is asking that question. Do you want
to be healed? Do you want to follow me for the rest
of your life? Do you want to serve me? Do you want
to fulfill the purpose that I have for you? >> Why is he
asking you that? Because is going to require you to get up
and move from where you are to where God is calling you
to be. Yes, that is the vision and the purpose of this
church. How many of you guys would would say tonight that you
are in a position where God is asking you to do something
that may be uncomfortable that that may be something that requires you
to make a change that you're not sure about yet. Remember the
Bible says count the cost. Count the cost before you start. There's
something powerful in consecration and saying, "Lord, I will do whatever you
ask me to do." >> Thank you, Lord. >> Amen. >> Thank you, Jesus. >> Would
that qualify to anybody here today? >> Thank you, Jesus. Thank you, Jesus.
>> Thank you, Jesus. >> Come, come forward >> if you would if that applies
to you here today.
>> Thank you, Lord. >> Thank you, Jesus. Thank you, Lord. >> Thank you, Lord.
>> Thank you, Lord. >> It requires boldness to step out to answer that
question truthfully. >> Thank you, Lord. >> Because it means that you're not willing
to sit there any longer. >> Thank you, Jesus. >> Amen. >> Amen. And L,
I want to say something before we pray. We're anointed to do
this, by the way. The spirit of the Lord is upon us.
We're anointed. This ministry is anointed. You know what this ministry is anointed
to do? exactly what he just said. Move people from where they
are to where God's called them to be. That's the word he
spoke over this church. So as we lay hands on you, that
anointing is on you. You're a part of this church. Father, in
the name. Go ahead and pray, John. >> Amen. >> In the name. >> So
tonight, the Lord asks you that question. >> Will you choose me? Will
you choose the plan that I have for you? Will you step
out beyond where you've been? because there's a place for you. >> Thank
you. >> There's a place beyond [music] where you've been that he wants
for you. So say yes. >> Say yes tonight. And he will cause
you to grow. He will cause you to go beyond where you've
been. >> And you will go further than you ever imagined. >> The Bible
says that we do not know the plans that he has for
us. the the fullness, the wonders, the the the greatness of it
because it it requires us to step out >> to step out to
see it one step at a time. So I believe tonight there
is an anointing on you that there is a grace on you
>> to step out and go beyond where you've been before in Jesus
name. >> In the name of Jesus. >> Amen. >> Amen. Amen. Thank you Lord.
Praise you father. Thank you Lord. Praise you, Father. Kaylee, can we
pray for you? Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord. I just felt
impressed. Is it okay if we just do this, guys? Is it
okay if we just just are led by the spirit for just
a moment? It's okay if you say, "No, I'm going to do it
anyway." So, praise God. I just Good practice. I don't know. The
Lord just want me to pray over you. Thank you, Lord. Father,
in the name of Jesus. Oh, this is what I hear the
Lord saying right now. The spirit of the Lord is upon you
because he's anointed you. He's anointed you in ways that you haven't
thought you were. He's anointed you in aspects in in uh abilities
that that you thought weren't in you that you thought you didn't
have. But the Lord is saying, "Hey, I put those things there."
And those things that you've seen in your heart already that you've
seen yourself doing and you thought, "Oh, no. I'm no that." No,
no. Those things that you've seen you doing and And I sure
hear the Lord saying this too. Your family doing your family doing.
This is not just a Kaye thing. This is a family thing.
Thank you, Lord. Oh, he's working in your family right now in
the name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord. This is a family anointing.
The family will be ministering together. The family will Thank you, Lord.
We pray over their entire Let's pray over their whole family. Your
whole family right now in the name of Jesus. Oh, for Kevin,
for cash. Thank you, Lord, for Thank you, Lord. Oh, yes. Thank
you, Jesus. In the name of Jesus. We thank you, Lord, over
every one of them. Thank you, Lord, for Colby. In the name
of Jesus, the anointing is on her as well. Thank you, Jesus.
Thank you, Father. Thank you, Lord. To do what you've called them
to do.
Oh, it's a season right now that you're in, but the Lord
says seasons change. Seasons change. You're not going to be in this
season forever. Seasons change. He's already working. He's already moving. And you
don't you don't you're not going to see it all in the
natural. You're not going to see things change overnight, just [music] like
the changing of seasons don't just change overnight. But gradually, you'll see
the season beginning to change. Just like in the spring, you start
to see flowers starting to bloom, trees starting to bloom, and you'll
be like, "Wow, it's a little cool outside, but look at that.
Look at that. Things [music] are beginning to change. You'll see the
same thing in your family. You'll begin to see the same thing.
Oh, thank you, Lord. Things are changing. The anointing The anointing is
on. The anointing is on your family because God doesn't just call
individuals, he calls families. Thank you, Lord, for that anointing on our
life in the name of Jesus. Praise you, Father. Thank you, Lord.
Let's give the Lord a hand for that one. Thank you, Jesus.
Thank you, Father. Thank you, Lord. We serve a good God. Amen.
Thank you, Lord.
Let's just pray for a minute. Thank you Lord. Thank you Jesus.
>> Thank you Lord. >> Thank you Jesus. >> Thank you Lord. To say that
I had dental work done today and it's been hurting pretty much
ever since. [music] And then when we were praying even coming up
here it just kept hurting and kept hurting and just in the
midst of praying he's [music] completely gone. So I don't have any
more pain. So I'm very thankful for that. So >> thank you >> just
being in the anointing. >> Amen. See, you can minister under the anointing
when you're having physical pain yourself. Well, that's a good word for
somebody. That's a good word for somebody. Some of y'all disqualified yourself
because of your condition. Or you said, "No, I experienced this and
I have this problem, so I can't minister to nobody." That's a
lie from the pit of hell. That same anointing in you will
heal your body and flow into somebody else and heal their body.
Thank you, Jesus, for it. Thank you, Lord, for healing teeth, toothaches
in the name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord. Oh,
you're such a good father. You're such a good father. Thank you,
Jesus.
Thank you, Lord. >> Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Jesus.
Chains broken [singing and music] hearts open you
[singing] are healed in Jesus name. >> Chains
be [singing and music] broken hearts be open. You [singing] are
healed in Jesus name. Chains be
broken, [singing] hearts [music] be open. You are healed
in Jesus [singing] name. Hearts be [singing]
eyes be.
>> Thank you Jesus name. [singing] >> Thank you Lord. I want everybody to
say this with me. The spirit of the Lord >> The Spirit of
the Lord >> is upon me. >> is upon me. >> You've anointed me. >> You've
anointed me >> to preach the gospel >> preach the gospel >> to the poor.
>> You've anointed me >> You've anointed me >> to lay hands >> to lay hands
>> on blind eyes >> on blind eyes. >> You've anointed me >> You've anointed me
>> to cast out demons >> to cast out [music] demons >> in the name
>> In the name >> of Jesus. of Jesus, >> the anointed one. >> The anointed
one >> with his anointing >> with his anointing. >> Thank you, Lord. Thank you,
Father. >> Oh, thank you, Lord. >> Thank you, Jesus. >> I just hear the
Lord saying this, too.
You need to know who you are.
If you only knew who you were and whose you were, renew
your mind to it.
Who do you belong to? Who's anointed you? That should drive out
all fear of failure. Drive out all fear of stepping out in
faith. God, his anointing is on your life. Use
it. Use it. You're anointed to go to work tomorrow. Praise you,
Father. Don't Don't dread it. You're anointed to do it. You're anointed
to fix problems nobody [music] else can fix. You're anointed to have
ideas out of your spirit that nobody's thought about. We got [music]
a problem. We need a new idea. The anointing will bring you
an idea. Thank you, Lord. I heard the Lord saying this. The
church has not operated in this anointing as they should. And this
is just a little sample tonight. You can operate under this anointing
all the time. The anointing is not just for healing. The supernatural
power, this anointing that's on your life is to do to do
what? Whatever is needed. It's kind of like spiritual gifts. They say, "Which
one's the best spiritual gift?" It's the one that's needed at the
time. You're anointed to do that one. God's anointed you for such
a time as this. Amen. I want to pray over everybody before
we go. Father, in the name of Jesus, I thank you for
this church. Oh, it's an anointed church. Powerful church. Thank you, Lord,
for the anointing on every single person's life here tonight. I thank
you, Lord, that we tonight are coming up to a new level,
functioning in, operating with, cooperating with you in that anointing. And that
everything that we do in this life from this point forward, everything
that we are challenged with, every time that we feel like we're
not enough, we feel like we can't, that's when we connect with
that anointing. That's when the anointing takes over and we say, "I
can do all things. Not in my own strength, not in my
own ability, but through Christ and his anointing. The anointed one and
his anointing on my life is enabling me to go do all
that you've called me to do to be the Christian you've called
me to be in the name of Jesus. We thank you for
it. We praise you for it in Jesus name. Praise you, Father.
I don't like to close services like this. I just like to
keep going. Amen. Praise God. Thank you, Lord. Isn't God good? Amen.
He's a good father. Invite someone to church this Sunday. I know
it's Mother's Day. You have something else to say, >> Miss Francis Marie.
You know, tomorrow is her birthday. She has to come here. [laughter]
>> If I know it's your birthday, you better watch out. >> Let's have
an anointed song, shall we? >> We love her. She's been a part
of our church for many [music] years and a huge blessing. And
we love you and we just want to honor you. So, we're
gonna sing happy birthday. >> Here we go. Happy birthday [singing] to you.
Happy birthday to you. >> Happy birthday, Princess Marie.
[laughter] >> Happy birthday to you.
>> All right. Thank you guys. You guys are dismissed. God bless y'all.
Hey, we [music] also need to get the sanctuary ready for school
tomorrow. So, if you have time to help with the chairs, that
would be awesome.
over. We sing hallelu. We sing hallelu.
We sing hallelu. [singing and music] The lamb is over. We
sing hallelu. We sing [singing] hallelu. We sing
[music] hallelu.